UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup III: Office of the President, 1971-1997; 3; 35.20
  - Series 3: Projects/Subjects -- Samuel Wakshull, 1971-May 1981; 3.3; 7.0
    - Subseries 3.1 - Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1971-May 1981; 1975-May 1981; 3.3.1; 5.33
      - Chancellor's Office-Labor-Management Meetings [RESTRICTED], July 1975-October 1978 (Box III.3.2, Folder 2)
      - Chancellor's Office-Master Plan [RESTRICTED], October 1974-July 1976 (Box III.3.2, Folder 3)
      - Chancellor's Office-Master Plan [RESTRICTED], October 1979 (Box III.3.2, Folder 4)
      - Chancellor's Office-Naples, Caesar (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Personnel and Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-June 1976 (Box III.3.2, Folder 5)
      - Chancellor's Office-Peterson, Thomas (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Academic Personnel) [RESTRICTED], November 1975-July 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 6)
      - Chancellor's Office-Schmidt, Dolores (Assistant Vice Chancellor for Affirmative Action) [RESTRICTED], February 1978 (Box III.3.2, Folder 7)
      - Chancellor's Office-Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], October 1977-October 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 8)
      - Chapter Questionnaires [RESTRICTED], October 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 9)
      - cIcu [Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities]-lobbyists for [RESTRICTED], January 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 10)
      - *Collective Bargaining-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1965; 1975-1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 11)
      - College and University Council (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box III.3.2, Folder 12)
      - College and University Task Force (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box III.3.2, Folder 13)
      - College Year Obligation/Appointments [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box III.3.2, Folder 14)
      - Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box III.3.2, Folder 15)
      - Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification; Report on Teaching as a Profession and Teacher Competence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box III.3.2, Folder 16)
      - *Committee on Residents and Interns [RESTRICTED], October 1978-January 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 17)
      - Committees-Affirmative Action (SUNY and UUP) [RESTRICTED], April 1975-March 1981 (Box III.3.2, Folder 18)
      - Committees-Appointments/Lists [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 19)
      - Committees-Attendance reporting for committee work [RESTRICTED], November 1979-December 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 20)
      - Committees-Career Development [RESTRICTED], September 1979-December 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 21)
      - Committees-Constitutional Review [RESTRICTED], October 1978-February 1979 (Box III.3.2, Folder 22)
      - Committees-Elections and Credentials [RESTRICTED], August 1975-November 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 23)
      - Committees-Extra Service Compensation [RESTRICTED], October 1977-October 1978 (Box III.3.2, Folder 24)
      - Committees-Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], February 1975-May 1981 (Box III.3.2, Folder 25)
      - Committees-Grievance [RESTRICTED], February 1979-July 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 26)
      - Committees-Legislation [RESTRICTED], August 1975-April 1978 (Box III.3.2, Folder 27)
      - Committees-Legislation [RESTRICTED], July 1978-April 1981 (Box III.3.2, Folder 28)
      - Committees-Membership Development/Membership Benefits [RESTRICTED], February 1979-December 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 29)
      - Committees-Negotiations [RESTRICTED], June 1978-March 1979 (Box III.3.2, Folder 30)
      - Committees-Retirement [RESTRICTED], June 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 31)
      - Committees-Retraining [RESTRICTED], October 1976-March 1981 (Box III.3.2, Folder 32)
      - Committees-Student Recruitment [RESTRICTED], March 1980-November 1980 (Box III.3.2, Folder 33)
      - Community Health Plan/Health Maintenance Organizations [RESTRICTED], October 1975-August 1976 (Box III.3.2, Folder 34)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Brockport [RESTRICTED], undated (Box III.3.2, Folder 35)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Brockport [RESTRICTED], November 1974 (Box III.3.2, Folder 36)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-State University College at Buffalo program [RESTRICTED], October 1984 (Box III.3.2, Folder 37)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Oswego and Cortland programs [RESTRICTED], November 1974 (Box III.3.2, Folder 38)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Proposed Program Leading to B.S. Degree and N-6 Provisional Certification, SUNY Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], November 1974 (Box III.3.2, Folder 39)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Proposed Program Leading to B.S. Degree and N-9 Provisional Certification, SUNY Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], November 1974 (Box III.3.2, Folder 40)
      - *Competency-Based Teacher Education (CBTE)-Old Westbury program [RESTRICTED], March 1974 (Box III.3.3, Folder 1)
      - *Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) [RESTRICTED], 1978; 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 2)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) positions/employees [RESTRICTED], January 1978-March 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 3)
      - Conference on Faculty Unions in Public Higher Education [RESTRICTED], October 1976-May 1977 (Box III.3.3, Folder 4)
      - Conferences [RESTRICTED], October 1977-February 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 5)
      - Communications Workers of America (CWA) [RESTRICTED], September 1977-November 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 6)
      - Delegate Assembly-Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box III.3.3, Folder 6A)
      - Dental Insurance [RESTRICTED], October 1979-March 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 7)
      - Dental Insurance Review Committee [RESTRICTED], January 1980-April 1981 (Box III.3.3, Folder 8)
      - *Department Rep Handbook [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 9)
      - Discretionary Funds [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box III.3.3, Folder 10)
      - Empire State Day Care Services, Inc.-Children's Place at the Plaza [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box III.3.3, Folder 11-12)
      - Executive Board [RESTRICTED], May 1975-May 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 13)
      - Executive Board-Minutes [RESTRICTED], February 1976; October-November 1976 (Box III.3.3, Folder 14)
      - Executive Budget (NYS) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 15)
      - Executive Committee (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], January 1978-May 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 16)
      - Executive Committee (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], June 1978-September 1979 (Box III.3.3, Folder 17)
      - *Extra Service Compensation (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 18)
      - *Extra Service Compensation (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 19)
      - Florida [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box III.3.3, Folder 20)
      - *"Focus on the Issues" lecture series [RESTRICTED], October 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 21)
      - *"Government and Higher Education in New York State", by Joseph A. Kershaw, prepared for Sloan Commission on Government and Higher Education [RESTRICTED], ca. February 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 22)
      - Grievances [RESTRICTED], March 1978-December 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 23)
      - Hobart, Thomas (NYSUT President) [RESTRICTED], May 1978-May 1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 24)
      - Huyler, David Erle (and other union-objectors) [RESTRICTED], September 1977 (Box III.3.3, Folder 25)
      - Improper Practice-Empire State-State of New York motions and correspondence [RESTRICTED], March-May 1976 (Box III.3.3, Folder 26)
      - Improper Practice-Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], May-June 1976 (Box III.3.3, Folder 27)
      - Inservice Education, Invitational Conference on [RESTRICTED], June-December 1977 (Box III.3.3, Folder 28)
      - Insurance, Group Life-Member correspondence [RESTRICTED], March 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 29)
      - Internship [RESTRICTED], November 1977 (Box III.3.3, Folder 30)
      - Job Vacancy Announcements-SUNY [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box III.3.3, Folder 31)
      - *Kaufman, Eugene (NYSUT counsel) [RESTRICTED], October 1977-January 1981 (Box III.3.3, Folder 32)
      - Kaufman, Eugene (NYSUT, General Counsel, Special Legal Services) [RESTRICTED], November 1977-September 1978 (Box III.3.3, Folder 33)
      - *Leadership Bulletins for chapter leadership [RESTRICTED], January 1978-July 1979 (Box III.3.3, Folder 34)
      - Legal Opinions-Miscellaneous and UUP specific [RESTRICTED], 1974-1980; 3 folders (Box III.3.3, Folder 35-37)
      - Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1981 (Box III.3.3, Folder 38)
      - *Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box III.3.3, Folder 39)
      - *Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box III.3.3, Folder 40)
      - *Legislative Days 1977 [RESTRICTED], February-June 1977 (Box III.3.4, Folder 1)
      - Legislative Day [RESTRICTED], March 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 2)
      - *Levittown Decision, The Evidence and the Conclusions (NYSUT report) [RESTRICTED], April 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 3)
      - Librarians [Academic Status] and UUP Task Force on Librarians' Concerns [RESTRICTED], October 1974-December 1975 (Box III.3.4, Folder 4)
      - Librarians [Academic Status] [RESTRICTED], May 1977-June 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 5)
      - *Life Insurance mailing to bargaining unit members [RESTRICTED], January 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 6)
      - *Lobbyist Statement of Registration-UUP [RESTRICTED], March 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 7)
      - McGrath, Thomas (Grievance) [RESTRICTED], December 1974; September 1976-December 1976 (Box III.3.4, Folder 8)
      - Managerial/Confidential [RESTRICTED], October 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 9)
      - Membership-Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 10)
      - Membership-Insurance, benefits, and other [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 11)
      - *Milton, John-public relations consultant [RESTRICTED], July 1980-July 1981 (Box III.3.4, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence [RESTRICTED], April 1975-May 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous [Wakshull personal correspondence?] [RESTRICTED], 1970s (Box III.3.4, Folder 14)
      - *NEA [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box III.3.4, Folder 15)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box III.3.4, Folder 16-17)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Albany Student Press [RESTRICTED], September-October 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 18)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Charles Baker [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 19)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], October 1977-October 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 20)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], December 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 21)
      - *NEA/NYEA-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-March 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 22)
      - *NEA/NYEA and SUNY Alliance [RESTRICTED], October 1977-February 1981 (Box III.3.4, Folder 23)
      - Negotiations Bulletins [RESTRICTED], October 1975-November 1976 (Box III.3.4, Folder 24)
      - Negotiations-Proposals, Committee, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 25)
      - Negotiations-Reopened [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box III.3.4, Folder 26)
      - New Rank for Academics [RESTRICTED], October 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 27)
      - New York Educators Association (NYEA) [RESTRICTED], February 1979-November 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 28)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], April 1975-March 1976 (Box III.3.4, Folder 29)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], April 1976-February 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 30)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT)-Board of Directors [RESTRICTED], September 1976-October 1977 (Box III.3.4, Folder 31)
      - Newsletter-"From the President's Log" [RESTRICTED], February 1976-June 1976 (Box III.3.4, Folder 32)
      - Newspaper clippings [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box III.3.4, Folder 33)
      - Non-Teaching Professionals (NTP) [RESTRICTED], 1976; 1978; 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 34)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 35)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Counsel [RESTRICTED], November 1976-October 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 35A)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Frucher, Meyer (Director) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-September 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 36)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Hartnett, Thomas (Deputy Director) [RESTRICTED], November 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 37)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Hodes, Nancy (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], July 1979-May 1980 (Box III.3.4, Folder 38)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Kershaw, Leonard (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], July 1977-December 1978 (Box III.3.4, Folder 39)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Northrop, James (Deputy Director) [RESTRICTED], September 1978-May 1979 (Box III.3.4, Folder 40)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Wollett, Donald (Director) [RESTRICTED], October 1975-October 1978 (Box III.3.5, Folder 1)
      - OMB Circular A-21-Cost principles for educational institutions/personnel activity reporting system [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 2)
      - *Our State-NYSUT newsletter (saved for NEA coverage?) [RESTRICTED], October 1976-March 1978 (Box III.3.5, Folder 3)
      - *Parking [RESTRICTED], May 1978-September 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 4)
      - Patent Policy (SUNY) and UUP Patent Waiver Policy Committee [RESTRICTED], November 1975-April 1977; April 1979-October 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 5)
      - Potsdam-National Center for Higher Education Management Systems survey/reorganization job descriptions [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box III.3.5, Folder 6)
      - Powell, Elwin (SUNY Buffalo) (academic freedom) [RESTRICTED], September 1976-February 1977 (Box III.3.5, Folder 7)
      - Project for Adult College Education (PACE) [RESTRICTED], October 1978-February 1981 (Box III.3.5, Folder 8)
      - Public Employees Federation (PEF) [RESTRICTED], July 1978-November 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 9)
      - Reform Caucus [RESTRICTED], October 5, 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 10)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], March 1976-December 1977 (Box III.3.5, Folder 11)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-June 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 12)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], August 1979-January 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 13)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], February 1980-August 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 14)
      - Representative Assembly (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], December 1976-March 1977 (Box III.3.5, Folder 15)
      - Research (miscellaneous? student/faculty ratios, workload, ranks) [RESTRICTED], December 1977-April 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 16)
      - Research Foundation (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], January 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 17)
      - Retraining Program/Retraining Committee [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 18)
      - Retrenchments [RESTRICTED], June 1975-May 1977; November 1979; March 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 19)
      - *Right to Work [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 20)
      - Salary Issues [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 21)
      - Save SUNY day/SUNY budget cut opposition [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box III.3.5, Folder 22-23)
      - *Senate Professional Association (SPA) [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Box III.3.5, Folder 24)
      - Senates (campus) [RESTRICTED], July 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 25)
      - *Sentry Insurance-Catastrophic Medical Coverage Plan [RESTRICTED], June-July 1978 (Box III.3.5, Folder 26)
      - Staff (NYSUT field staff and UUP admin. office) [RESTRICTED], 1975-May 1978 (Box III.3.5, Folder 27)
      - Staff (NYSUT field staff and UUP admin. office) [RESTRICTED], June 1978-November 1979; December 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 28)
      - *State University Professional Association [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box III.3.5, Folder 29)
      - Statewide Coalition for Public Higher Education [RESTRICTED], December 1980-February 1981 (Box III.3.5, Folder 30)
      - Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-December 1980 (Box III.3.5, Folder 31)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box III.3.5, Folder 32)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box III.3.5, Folder 33)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 3 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box III.3.5, Folder 34)
      - *SUNY Budget/UUP Budget 1978-79 [RESTRICTED], January-November 1978 (Box III.3.5, Folder 35)
      - *SUNY Budget 1979-80 [RESTRICTED], February-December 1979 (Box III.3.5, Folder 36)
      - *SUNY Budget 1980-81 (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], December 1979-June 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 1)
      - *SUNY Budget 1980-81 (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], October 1979-February 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 2)
      - SUNY-CUNY Merger/Wessell Commission [Temporary State Commission on the Future of Post-Secondary Education] [RESTRICTED], January-April 1977; July-September 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 3)
      - SUNY Day Care Centers [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box III.3.6, Folder 4)
      - SUNY Policy-Award of Academic Credit by Examination [RESTRICTED], July-August 1976 (Box III.3.6, Folder 5)
      - TIAA-CREF (Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association/College Retirement Equity Fund) [RESTRICTED], 1979; 1981 (Box III.3.6, Folder 6)
      - Unity Caucus [RESTRICTED], June 1976-April 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 7)
      - Universitas (newsletter-University Professors for Academic Order) [RESTRICTED], October 1978-June 1979 (Box III.3.6, Folder 8)
      - *Update-newsletter for local leaders of NYSUT [RESTRICTED], April 1976-June 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 9)
      - UUP Budget [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 10)
      - *UUP Office [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976; 1982 (Box III.3.6, Folder 11)
      - UUP Project Expenses/Budget [RESTRICTED], September 1977-December 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 12)
      - VOTE/COPE [RESTRICTED], March 1978-April 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 13)
      - *Wakshull article-Labor Law Journal (NEA related) [RESTRICTED], March 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 14)
      - Workload [RESTRICTED], September 1976-October 1976 (Box III.3.6, Folder 15)
      - *Zelden, Marvin (Editor, universitas) [RESTRICTED], July-September 1978; August-September 1979 (Box III.3.6, Folder 16)
    - Subseries 3.2 - Administrative Files [RESTRICTED], 1971-April 1981; 1975-April 1981; 3.3.2; 1.67
      Incoming and outgoing correspondence from UUP's President, Executive Director, and other UUP personnel; as well as internal correspondence between the President, Executive Director, membership coordinator, and NYSUT legal counsel. Materials were filed by chapter involved, under individual name (relating to grievance matters, and also for UUP personnel matters), and occasionally by subject. Topics covered include retrenchments on campuses; appointments to and resignations from committees; campus specific concerns; grievances; questions from members regarding benefits and membership; resolutions sent in by chapters; minutes for chapter board meetings as well as chapter labor/management meetings; and information on chapter officers. The amount and type of information available for each chapter varies widely. Additional records on individual chapters make up Subseries 3.3 in Subgroup IV, Office of the Secretary. Agency fee issues and the separation of UUP from NEA are infrequent topics of discussion. The records for the Grievance Committee in this series include reports to the President presenting the committee's position on/view of the grievances under its consideration. These reports provide some of the most detailed information available regarding the issues that UUP has sought to remedy through grievances on behalf of its bargaining unit members.
      One recurring concern reflected in the President's correspondence with chapter leaders is the reasons behind the resignation of UUP members, particularly as UUP was seeking during this period to shore up its membership not only to defeat the NEA/NYEA and other challengers, but to provide the strongest front possible for future contract negotiations. Although the bulk of the materials in this series cover the Wakshull administration (1975-1981), this series also includes some documents from the DeLucia administration (1973-1975).
      - Albany Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1974-November 1975 (Box III.3.6, Folder 17)
      - Albany Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1977-January 1981 (Box III.3.6, Folder 18)
      - Alfred Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-February 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 19)
      - Binghamton Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-June 1979 (Box III.3.6, Folder 20)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-May 1976 (Box III.3.6, Folder 21)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], June 1976-August 1977 (Box III.3.6, Folder 22)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1977-July 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 23)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1978-October 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 24)
      - Buffalo Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.6, Folder 25)
      - Buffalo Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1977-February 1981 (Box III.3.6, Folder 26)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], October 1975-October 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 27)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1975-December 1975 (Box III.3.6, Folder 28)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1976-October 1977 (Box III.3.6, Folder 29)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], November 1977-September 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 30)
      - Canton Chapter [RESTRICTED], December 1974-April 1980 (Box III.3.6, Folder 31)
      - Carey, Hugh (NYS Governor) and Office of Employee Relations [RESTRICTED], November 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.6, Folder 32)
      - Central Administration Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1975-October 1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 33)
      - Certification Program in Teacher Education/Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification [CBTE] [RESTRICTED], October 1974-April 1976 (Box III.3.6, Folder 34)
      - Chapter Leadership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box III.3.6, Folder 35)
      - Chapter Presidents [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1976 (Box III.3.6, Folder 36)
      - Chapter Presidents [RESTRICTED], August 1976-November 1979; September 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 1)
      - Cobleskill Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1976-November 1978 (Box III.3.7, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (union-wide) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1976 (Box III.3.7, Folder 3)
      - Cortland Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 4)
      - CSEA (Civil Service Employee Association) [RESTRICTED], December 1976-March 1979 (Box III.3.7, Folder 5)
      - CUNY (City University of New York) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1977 (Box III.3.7, Folder 6)
      - Delhi Chapter [RESTRICTED], June 1975-March 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 7)
      - Downstate Medical Center [Brooklyn] Chapter [RESTRICTED], November 1975-February 1978 (Box III.3.7, Folder 8)
      - Downstate Medical Center [Brooklyn] Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1978-April 1981 (Box III.3.7, Folder 9)
      - Empire State College Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 10)
      - Environmental Science and Forestry Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1977-August 1978 (Box III.3.7, Folder 11)
      - Executive Board [RESTRICTED], May 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 12)
      - Farmingdale Chapter [RESTRICTED], May 1975-December 1977 (Box III.3.7, Folder 13)
      - Farmingdale Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1978-March 1980 (Box III.3.7, Folder 14)